Finding Aid for the George P. Johnson Negro Film Collection LSC.1042
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Research Files
  - H
    - Hyman, Earle
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 375, P.O.W. (Reel 10)
    - Hyson, Robert
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 466, Christie Comedies. (Reel 2)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 373, Melancholy Dame. (Reel 8)
    - Hyson, Roberta
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 144-149, Georgia Rose. (Reel 1)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 466-467, Christie Comedies. (Reel 2)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 70. (Reel 6)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 149, The Lady Fare. (Reel 7)
  - I
    - I Accused
      See The Accused
    - I am a Champion, Frame(s) 72, Kid Gavilan. (Reel 6)
    - I Crossed the Colored Line, Frame(s) 73. (Reel 6)
    - I Dood It, Frame(s) 74. (Reel 6)
    - I Dream of Jeannie, Frame(s) 75, Louise Beavers. (Reel 6)
    - I Hate Your Guts, Frame(s) 76. (Reel 6)
    - I Like It That Way, Frame(s) 77, Clarence Wilson. (Reel 6)
    - I Love You Alive, Frame(s) 78, Leroy Glenn. (Reel 6)
    - I Passed for White, Frame(s) 398. (Reel 1)
    - I Passed for White
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 166, radio commercial. (Reel 2)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 245, Joe Green. (Reel 5)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 79-81. (Reel 6)
    - I Shot Jessie James, Frame(s) 82, Jeni LeGon. (Reel 6)
    - I Shot Johnny Ringo, Frame(s) 83. (Reel 6)
    - I Walked with a Zombie, Frame(s) 84. (Reel 6)
    - I was a Prisoner in Korea, Frame(s) 85. (Reel 6)
    - I Was a Prisoner of War, Frame(s) 86-87. (Reel 6)
    - I Wonder Who's Kissing Her Now, Frame(s) 88. (Reel 6)
    - Ice Station Zebra, Frame(s) 89. (Reel 6)
    - If He Hollers, Let Him Go, Frame(s) 90. (Reel 6)
    - If I Should Die, Before I Wake, Frame(s) 91, Ruth Cross. (Reel 6)
    - If This is Tuesday, It Must Be Belgium, Frame(s) 92, Sammy Davis, Jr. (Reel 6)
    - I'll Never Come Back, Frame(s) 93. (Reel 6)
    - I'll Fix It, Frame(s) 94. (Reel 6)
    - Image Awards of Beverly Hills, Frame(s) 504, Negro entertainers. (Reel 4)
    - Imitation of Life, (1934)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 55. (Reel 1)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 106. (Reel 6)
    - Imitation of Life, (1957)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 95-105. (Reel 6)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 686, Juanita Moore. (Reel 8)
    - The Imposter, Frame(s) 107. (Reel 6)
    - The Impressions, Frame(s) 108. (Reel 6)
    - In Cold Blood, Frame(s) 109, Scott Wilson. (Reel 6)
    - In Old Chicago, Frame(s) 110, Naomi Sultewan. (Reel 6)
    - In Old Kentucky, (1927); Frame(s) 111, list of players. (Reel 6)
    - In Old Kentucky, (1935); Frame(s) 112, Bill Robinson. (Reel 6)
    - In the Depths of Our Hearts
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 113-4. (Reel 6)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 375-6, Royal Garden Film Company. (Reel 11)
    - In the Heat of the Night, Frame(s) 115-21. (Reel 6)
    - In the Meantime, Darling, Frame(s) 122, Clarence Muse. (Reel 6)
    - In the Palace of the King, Frame(s) 123. (Reel 6)
    - In This Our Life, Frame(s) 124, Ernest Anderson. (Reel 6)
    - Incantevale Menica, Frame(s) 125, Benjamin Turpin. (Reel 6)
    - The Incident, Frame(s) 126-7. (Reel 6)
    - Incident on the Campus, Frame(s) 128. (Reel 6)
    - The Inevitable, Frame(s) 129. (Reel 6)
    - The Infamy, Frame(s) 130. (Reel 6)
    - The Informer, Frame(s) 131. (Reel 6)
    - Inqagi, Frame(s) 132. (Reel 6)
    - Ingram, Clifford
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 469-75, Hearts in Dixie. (Reel 5)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 134. (Reel 6)
    - Ingram, Rex
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 464-7, Christie Comedies. (Reel 2)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 149, writer. (Reel 3)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 135-44 *. (Reel 6)
    - Inherit the Wind, Frame(s) 145. (Reel 6)
    - The Ink Spots
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 50, Shep Allen. (Reel 1)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 16. (Reel 5)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 16, touring; 146-147; 632, Bill Kenny. (Reel 6)
    - Insidious Dr. Fu Manchu, Frame(s) 148. (Reel 6)
    - International Negro Newsreel, Frame(s) 149, Chappie Gardner. (Reel 6)
    - International Revue, Frame(s) 150. (Reel 6)
    - International Road Show, Frame(s) 151-152. (Reel 6)
    - The Interns, Frame(s) 153. (Reel 6)
    - Interracial Singers Synanon Foundation, Frame(s) 435. (Reel 1)
    - Intolerance, Frame(s) 154-155. (Reel 6)
    - The Intruder, (1956); Frame(s) 160. (Reel 6)
    - The Intruder, (1962); Frame(s) 156-159. (Reel 6)
    - Intruder in the Dust, Frame(s) 161. (Reel 6)
    - Interrupted Melody, Frame(s) 162. (Reel 6)
    - Invisible Ray, Frame(s) 163, Etta McDaniels. (Reel 6)
    - Irish Luck, Frame(s) 164, Mantan Moreland. (Reel 6)
    - Irma La Douce
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 165. (Reel 6)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 544, Herb Jones. (Reel 6)
    - The Iron Man, Frame(s) 166. (Reel 6)
    - The Iron Mistress, Frame(s) 167, Ernest Anderson. (Reel 6)
    - Ironside, Frame(s) 168. (Reel 6)
    - Is My Face Red?, Frame(s) 169. (Reel 6)
    - Island in the Sun, Frame(s) 170-175. (Reel 6)
    - Island Interlude, Frame(s) 176, Johnny Mathis. (Reel 6)
    - Island of Shame, Frame(s) 177. (Reel 6)
    - The Islanders, Frame(s) 178. (Reel 6)
    - Isn't It Romantic, Frame(s) 179, Pearly Bailey. (Reel 6)
    - Istanbul, Frame(s) 180. (Reel 6)
    - It Happened on Sunday, Frame(s) 18, Robert Abrams. (Reel 1)
    - The Italian Job, Frame(s) 18, Quincy Jones. (Reel 6)
    - It's a Mad, Mad...World, Frame(s) 182-183, Eddie Anderson. (Reel 6)
    - It's a Wonderful Life, Frame(s) 184, Jester Hairson Choir. (Reel 6)
    - It's Good Business, Frame(s) 185-8. (Reel 6)
    - It's Tough to be Famous, Frame(s) 189, Louise Beavers. (Reel 6)
    - It's Trad, Dad, Frame(s) 190, Chubby Checker. (Reel 6)
    - It's Up to You, Frame(s) 191. (Reel 6)
    - It's Your Thing, Frame(s) 508, Negro entertainers. (Reel 4)
    - Ivory Hunter, Frame(s) 192, Orlando Martinus. (Reel 6)
  - J
    - Jack Johnson Film, Frame(s) 193. (Reel 6)
    - Jackie Robinson Story, Frame(s) 194. (Reel 6)
    - Jackpot Jitters, Frame(s) 195, Willie Best. (Reel 6)
    - Jackson, Al
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 26, Boy, What a Girl. (Reel 2)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 511, Herald Pictures. (Reel 5)
    - Jackson, Arlene, Frame(s) 196-7. (Reel 6)
    - Jackson, Calvin
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 198-200. (Reel 6)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 317, Tormented. (Reel 12)
    - Jackson, Dan, Frame(s) 201, Roots of Heaven. (Reel 6)
    - Jackson, Dynamite (Ernest), Frame(s) 203. (Reel 6)
    - Jackson, Earl, Frame(s) 202, Rachael Cade. (Reel 6)
    - Jackson, Eugene, W. III
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 204-8. (Reel 6)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 599-603, Shenandoah. (Reel 11)
    - Jackson, Eugene, W. Jr., Frame(s) 204-8 *. (Reel 6)
    - Jackson, Freddie, Frame(s) 236, Argus Pictures. (Reel 1)
    - Jackson, Hal, Frame(s) 335, Rockin' the Blues. (Reel 11)
    - Jackson, Horace
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 561. (Reel 1)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 733-36. (Reel 7)
    - Jackson, James A., Frame(s) 209. (Reel 6)
    - Jackson, Jesse, Frame(s) 344, Josephine Baker. (Reel 1)
    - Jackson, Mahalia
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 462; 495; 555, The Best Man. (Reel 1)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 553-554. (Reel 2)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 210-246; 267, Jazz on a Summer Day. (Reel 6)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 424-438, St. Louis Blues. (Reel 11)
    - Jackson, Mary Ann, Frame(s) 97. (Reel 3)
    - Jackson Motion Picture Company, Frame(s) 249. (Reel 6)
    - Jackson, Quentin, Frame(s) 247. (Reel 2)
    - Jackson, Samanda, Frame(s) 247, Something of Value. (Reel 6)
    - Jackson, Theron, Frame(s) 248. (Reel 6)
    - Jacquet, Illinois, Frame(s) 600, Nat King Cole. (Reel 2)
    - Jade Mask, Frame(s) 250, Mantan Moreland. (Reel 6)
    - Jaguar Nana, Frame(s) 251, Lee Henderson. (Reel 6)
    - Jam Session, Frame(s) 253. (Reel 6)
    - Jamaica
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 17, Joe Adams. (Reel 1)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 252, Lena Horne. (Reel 6)
    - Jamaica Sea, Frame(s) 254-256. (Reel 6)
    - James Brown Story, Frame(s) 261. (Reel 6)
    - James, Clifton, Frame(s) 644-648. (Reel 1)
    - James, Leon
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 236, Cabin in the Sky. (Reel 2)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 257. (Reel 6)
    - James, Olga
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 311-312, Carmen Jones. (Reel 2)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 469, Mr. Wonderful. (Reel 3)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 258-261. (Reel 6)
    - Jamison, Judith, Frame(s) 262. (Reel 6)
    - Janie, Frame(s) 263, Hattie McDaniel. (Reel 6)
    - Janie Gets Married, Frame(s) 264, Hattie McDaniel. (Reel 6)
    - Jasper, Frame(s) 265, John Henry. (Reel 6)
    - Jazz Dance Theatre Company, Frame(s) 556, Berry Brothers. (Reel 1)
    - Jazz on a Summer Day, Frame(s) 267. (Reel 6)
    - Jazz Scene, Frame(s) 268. (Reel 6)
    - The Jazz Sounds, Frame(s) 266. (Reel 6)
    - Jazz Train, Frame(s) 269. (Reel 6)
    - The Jazzman, Frame(s) 270, Lloyd Price. (Reel 6)
    - Jazzmobile, Frame(s) 505, Negro entertainers. (Reel 4)
    - Jedda, Frame(s) 271. (Reel 6)
    - Jeannette, Joe, Frame(s) 272, Square Joe. (Reel 6)
    - Jeffries, Herb
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 174 Movie Musicals. (Reel 1)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 273-280 *. (Reel 6)
    - Jemison, Diane, Frame(s) 281. (Reel 6)
    - Jenkins, Margaret, Frame(s) 394, Harlem in Heaven. (Reel 5)
    - Jessie James, [No further description available]. (Reel 282)
    - Jesse James, Frame(s) 283, Ernest Whitman. (Reel 6)
    - Jessye, Eva Mae
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 644-8, Black Like Me. (Reel 1)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 284. (Reel 6)
    - Jewel, Robbery, Frame(s) 285, Clarence Wilson. (Reel 6)
    - Jezebel, Frame(s) 288, Ike Jones. (Reel 6)
    - Joanna, (1968); Frame(s) 287. (Reel 6)
    - Joanna, (1969); Frame(s) 742-54, Calvin Lockhart. (Reel 7)
    - Joe Palooka in the Knockout, Frame(s) 286, Clarence Muse. (Reel 6)
    - Joey, Frame(s) 289. (Reel 6)
    - John Errol
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 235, Assault on a Queen. (Reel 1)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 291, Guns at Batasi. (Reel 5)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 290. (Reel 6)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 773, The Nun's Story. (Reel 9)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 730, PT 109. (Reel 10)
    - John Henry and Inky Poo, Frame(s) 292-5. (Reel 6)
    - John-Jay Company, Frame(s) 296. (Reel 6)
    - Johnnie Dark, Frame(s) 298, Scatman Crothers. (Reel 6)
    - Johnny Cool, Frame(s) 297, Sammy Davis, Jr. (Reel 6)
    - Johnny Mathis Story, Frame(s) 299. (Reel 6)
    - Johnny North, Frame(s) 300. (Reel 6)
    - Johnny Spielt Auf, Frame(s) 301. (Reel 6)
    - Johnson & Dean
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 144-149, Georgia Rose. (Reel 1)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 50, death. (Reel 2)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 48-51. (Reel 4)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 305, Johnson, Dora Dean. (Reel 6)
    - Johnson, Ben E., Dr.
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 128-130, Anna's Sin. (Reel 1)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 302. (Reel 6)
    - Johnson, Bob
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 303. (Reel 6)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 733-736, Living Between Two Worlds. (Reel 7)
    - Johnson, Bubber Quartet
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 304. (Reel 6)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 50, Red Ball Express. (Reel 11)
    - Johnson, Carlton, Frame(s) 352, Katherine Dunham. (Reel 4)
    - Johnson, Charles
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 50, Dora Dean. (Reel 2)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 48-51, Dora Dean. (Reel 4)
    - Johnson, Dots
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 306. (Reel 6)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 319, Paisan. (Reel 10)
    - Johnson, George P.
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 2, Robert Abrams, 238, Association Negro Picture Distribution. (Reel 1)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 111. (Reel 3)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 53-54, Deanwood Pictures Corp.; 385-392, Ebony Films Corp.; 678, Florentine Films; 690-701, William Foster. (Reel 4)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 24-26, Frederick Douglas Film Co. 48-55, French Pictorial Service; 86-87, Harry Gant; 548, Hilburn, Lincoln C. (Reel 5)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 307-443; 464-528, Noble Johnson. (Reel 6)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 178, Tony Langston; 327-715, Lincoln Motion Pictures Company. (Reel 7)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 392-562, Oscar Micheaux. (Reel 8)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 37, Motion Picture Industry. (Reel 9)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 197-303, Pacific Coast News Bureau. (Reel 10)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 505-515, Emmet Scott. (Reel 11)
    - Johnson, Hall, Frame(s) 44, death. (Reel 6)
    - Johnson, J.J., Frame(s) 445-449. (Reel 6)
    - Johnson, J. Rosamond
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 153, Henry Armstrong. (Reel 1)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 450. (Reel 6)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 910, Wm. Grant Still. (Reel 11)
    - Johnson, Jack
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 112-114; 635, For His Mother's Sake. (Reel 1)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 354, Ted Carroll drawing. (Reel 2)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 570, Fidelity Pictures; 673. (Reel 4)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 211, Gore and Igor. (Reel 5)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 193, Jack Johnson Story; 451-455; 553-576, James Earl Jones. (Reel 6)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 166-174, Sam Langford. (Reel 7)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 265-266, The Man in Ebony; 585-591, Millman Productions. (Reel 8)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 423-426, Negro boxers. (Reel 9)
    - Johnson, Julius, Frame(s) 456. (Reel 6)
    - Johnson, John Lester
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 497, Hell's Highway. (Reel 5)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 457. (Reel 6)
    - Johnson, Kyle
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 619, Joel Fluellen. (Reel 4)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 458-460. (Reel 6)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 733-736, Living Between Two Worlds. (Reel 7)
    - Johnson, Louis
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 272, Damn Yankees. (Reel 3)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 461, Damn Yankees. (Reel 6)
    - Johnson, Mae
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 153, Henry Armstrong. (Reel 1)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 216, Domino Productions. (Reel 4)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 463. (Reel 6)
    - Johnson, Marv
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 462. (Reel 6)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 155, Teen Age Millionaire. (Reel 12)
    - Johnson, Myra, Frame(s) 394, Harlem is Heaven. (Reel 5)
    - Johnson, Nobel
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 2, Robert Abrams; 238-9. (Reel 1)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 674, William Foster. (Reel 4)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 303-443, George Johnson; 464-528 *; 580 Phillip A. Jones. (Reel 6)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 329-715, Lincoln Motion Picture Company. (Reel 7)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 392-562, Oscar Micheaux. (Reel 8)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 37, Motion Picture Industry. (Reel 9)
    - Johnson, Rafer
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 581. (Reel 1)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 573, The Fiercest Heart. (Reel 4)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 529-39; 598, Journey into Danger. (Reel 6)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 719, The Lion. (Reel 7)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 560, Senegalese. (Reel 11)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 899, Wild in the Country. (Reel 12)
    - Johnson, Rubie Ursala
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 421, Count Basie. (Reel 1)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 540, Callaboo. (Reel 6)
    - Johnson, William, Frame(s) 117, Colored Players Film Company. (Reel 3)
    - Jones, Beulah Hall, Frame(s) 243, Drums Along the Mohawk. (Reel 4)
    - Jones, Booker T., Frame(s) 541. (Reel 6)
    - Jones, Carl, Frame(s) 542-3. (Reel 6)
    - Jones, Chester, Frame(s) 552, The Buccaneer. (Reel 6)
    - Jones, Darby, Frame(s) 548, list of films. (Reel 6)
    - Jones, Edna Mae
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 108, George White Scandals. (Reel 5)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 145, Ladies of Washington. (Reel 7)
    - Jones, Elvin
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 545. (Reel 6)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 10, The Long Stripe. (Reel 8)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 215, The Third Bird. (Reel 12)
    - Jones Film Company, Frame(s) 10, Motion Picture Industry. (Reel 9)
    - Jones, Gus
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 466-7, Christie Comedies. (Reel 2)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 149, The Lady Fare. (Reel 7)
    - Jones, Happy, Frame(s) 146-9. (Reel 6)
    - Jones, Hazel
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 569, The Big City. (Reel 1)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 545. (Reel 6)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 16, Strictly Personal; 194 Thanks for the Buggy Ride. (Reel 12)
    - Jones, Herb, Frame(s) 544, Irma La Douce. (Reel 6)
    - Jones, Ike
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 288, Jezebel; 549-51. (Reel 6)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 1, Kid from Left Field. (Reel 7)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 708-11, Prisoner of War. (Reel 10)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 44, Rebel Breed. (Reel 11)
    - Jones, James Earl
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 289, Moses Gunn; 193, Jack Johnson. (Reel 5)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 553-75 *. (Reel 6)
    - Jones, Judd, Frame(s) 203-206, Theatrical Booking Agencies. (Reel 12)
    - Jones, Ken, Frame(s) 577. (Reel 6)
    - Jones, LeRoi
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 184. (Reel 1)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 136-8, Confessions of Nat Turner. (Reel 3)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 576. (Reel 6)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 239, Sandra Lein. (Reel 7)
    - Jones, Margurite, Frame(s) 578, Rachel Cade. (Reel 6)
    - Jones, Matthew
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 38, Bread of Sea. (Reel 1)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 579 Bread of Sea. (Reel 6)
    - Jones, Oroville (Happy), Frame(s) 146-7, Ink Spots. (Reel 6)
    - Jones, Phillip A., Frame(s) 580. (Reel 6)
    - Jones, Quincy
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 688. (Reel 1)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 269, Godfrey Cambridge. (Reel 2)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 361, A Dandy in Aspic. (Reel 3)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 45, A Deadly Affair. (Reel 4)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 171, Gold. (Reel 5)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 31, House of Flowers; 181, The Italian Job; 589-597. (Reel 6)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 156, McKenna's Gold; 230, Made in Paris; 612, Mirage. (Reel 8)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 374-6, The Pawnbroker. (Reel 10)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 550, Seconds; 715, The Slender Thread. (Reel 11)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 273, Time for Heroes; 296, Tobruk; 717, Walk Don't Run. (Reel 12)
    - Jones, Richard M., Frame(s) 630, Footlite Magazine. (Reel 4)
    - Jones, Robert Earle, Frame(s) 581. (Reel 6)
    - Jones, Roland, Frame(s) 582, death. (Reel 6)
    - Jones, Sigsbee, Frame(s) 583, West of Zanzibar. (Reel 6)
    - Jones, Tamiko, Frame(s) 584. (Reel 6)
    - Jones, Thaddus, Frame(s) 588. (Reel 6)
    - Jordan, Louis
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 240-41. (Reel 1)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 397; 622, Follow the Boys. (Reel 4)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 402-429, Ray Charles. (Reel 2)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 585-586. (Reel 6)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 73, Swing Parade of 1946. (Reel 12)
    - Jordan, Rhoda
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 587, death. (Reel 6)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 253, 3 Blondes in his Life. (Reel 12)
    - Journey into Danger, Frame(s) 598. (Reel 6)
    - Journey to Shiloh, Frame(s) 599. (Reel 6)
    - Joyce, Brenda, Frame(s) 600. (Reel 6)
    - Joyner, Matilda
      See Black Pattie
    - Juarez, Frame(s) 601, Noble Johnson. (Reel 6)
    - Judge Priest, Frame(s) 602, Hattie McDaniels, Steppin Fetchit. (Reel 6)
    - Juke Box Jamboree, Frame(s) 603. (Reel 6)
    - Julian, Hubert, F., Frame(s) 604. (Reel 6)
    - Julien, Max
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 638-642, The Black Klansman. (Reel 1)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 438, Che. (Reel 2)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 605-606. (Reel 6)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 363-345, Julian Mayfield. (Reel 8)
    - Juliet Educational Film Company, Frame(s) 607-610. (Reel 6)
    - Juma, Frame(s) 611. (Reel 6)
    - Jumbo, Frame(s) 612, James Usher. (Reel 6)
    - Jump For Joy, Frame(s) 613. (Reel 6)
    - Jump, Jive and Wail, Frame(s) 614, Sammy Davis, Jr. (Reel 6)
    - Jungle Gents, Frame(s) 615. (Reel 6)
    - Jungle Girl, Frame(s) 616. (Reel 6)
    - Jungle Maneater, Frame(s) 617. (Reel 6)
    - Jungle Manhunt, Frame(s) 618. (Reel 6)
    - Jurokai, Frame(s) 619, Arthur Chico Laurent. (Reel 6)
  - K
    - Kahanamoku, Duke, Frame(s) 620. (Reel 6)
    - Kahn, Richard, Frame(s) 400, Harlem Rides the Range; 583 Hollywood Productions. (Reel 5)
    - Kalana, Thias Nehli, Frame(s) 115-128, Democracy Films Corporation. (Reel 4)
    - Kaleidoscope, Frame(s) 621. (Reel 6)
    - Kalu, Kalu, Frame(s) 623, Mark of the Hawk. (Reel 6)
    - Karamoju, Frame(s) 622. (Reel 6)
    - Keep Punching, Frame(s) 624, Henry Armstrong. (Reel 6)
    - Kell-Cole Productions
      - unspecified, Frame(s) Nat King Cole. (Reel 2)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) Nat King Cole. (Reel 3)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 549, Ike Jones. (Reel 6)
    - Kellerman, Annette, Frame(s) 73-74, Reformation. (Reel 11)
    - Kelly, Mahel
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 625. (Reel 6)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 574-577, Midnight Ace. (Reel 8)
    - Kelly, Paula, Frame(s) 626-630. (Reel 6)
    - Kennedy, Florence, Frame(s) 117, Colored Players Film Corporation. (Reel 3)
    - Kenner, Frame(s) 631. (Reel 6)
    - Kenny, Bill
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 50, Shep Allen. (Reel 1)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 146-147, Ink Spots; 632. (Reel 6)
    - Ker-Mar Picture Producing, Frame(s) 633-636. (Reel 6)
    - Key Witness, Frame(s) 637. (Reel 6)
    - Keystone Cops, Frame(s) 638. (Reel 6)
    - Khartoum, Frame(s) 639-640. (Reel 6)
    - Kid From Left Field, Frame(s) 1, Ike Jones. (Reel 7)
    - Kid Millions, Frame(s) 2, Stymie Beard. (Reel 7)
    - Kiku and Isamu, Frame(s) 3-5. (Reel 7)
    - Killebrew, Frank, Frame(s) 6. (Reel 7)
    - Killens, John O., Frame(s) 7-9. (Reel 7)
    - Killing Time, Frame(s) 10. (Reel 7)
    - Kilpatrick, Lincoln, Frame(s) 11. (Reel 7)
    - Kincaid, Jeremiah
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 12. (Reel 7)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 790. (Reel 11)
    - King, B.B.
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 223, Papa John Creach. (Reel 3)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 13. (Reel 7)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 511-512. (Reel 9)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 109, Talent for Love. (Reel 12)
    - King Creole, Frame(s) 21. (Reel 7)
    - King, Elmer, Frame(s) 14, Steamboat Bill, Jr. (Reel 7)
    - King, Jean
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 55, All The Fine Young Cannibals. (Reel 1)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 15. (Reel 7)
    - King Kong, (1933); Frame(s) 22, Noble Johnson. (Reel 7)
    - King, Mabel, Frame(s) 295, Hello Dolly. (Reel 1)
    - King, Martin Luther
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 26. (Reel 1)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 203, Ralph Bunche. (Reel 2)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 464-465, The Heart is a Lonely Hunter. (Reel 5)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 210-246, Mahalia Jackson. (Reel 6)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 16-19. (Reel 7)
    - King of Africa, Frame(s) 23. (Reel 7)
    - King of Burlesque, Frame(s) 24, Fats Waller. (Reel 7)
    - King of Kings, Frame(s) 25-30. (Reel 7)
    - King of Kings, Frame(s) 31. (Reel 7)
    - King of the Hill, Frame(s) 32. (Reel 7)
    - King Soloman's Mine, Frame(s) 18. (Reel 1)
    - King, Webb
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 144-149, Georgia Rose. (Reel 1)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 20; 422-717, Lincoln Motion Picture Company. (Reel 7)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 73-74, Reformation. (Reel 11)
    - Kingi, Henry, Frame(s) 33. (Reel 7)
    - Kings Go Forth, Frame(s) 36-40. (Reel 7)
    - Kings of the Sun, Frame(s) 41. (Reel 7)
    - Kings, Samba, Frame(s) 34-35, Romance on the High Seas. (Reel 7)
    - Kinkcaid, Gamble, Frame(s) 42-43. (Reel 7)
    - Kinky, Frame(s) 44. (Reel 7)
    - Kirby, George
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 254, Cab Calloway. (Reel 2)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 499, Negro entertainers. (Reel 4)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 45. (Reel 7)
    - Kirby, John, Frame(s) 511, Herald Pictures. (Reel 5)
    - Kirksey, Kirk
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 638-642, The Black Klansman. (Reel 1)